http://www.eao.com/privacy-policies/

HomeMarketsTransportationAutomotiveMachineryHeavy Duty & Special VehiclesMore marketsProducts
and solutionsHMI ComponentsHMI SystemsEAO AutomotiveProduction expertiseResearch and developmentQualityValue Added ServicesCertificates and approvalsProduction and supply chainAwards and recognitionReferencesNews and downloadsNews and press releasesTrade fairs and exhibitonsDownloadsPress enquiriesImagesAbout EAOThe companyManufacturing companiesThe Human Touch ®Swiss Touch ®Green TouchEAO GroupJobsContact usEAO worldwideContact formPress inquiriesJobs & Career
EAO Privacy Policies
Privacy Policies1. Protection of personal data
EAO attaches great importance to the protection of your personal data.
2. Handling of personal data
When you register on our website, you will be asked to provide certain details (your name, address and e-mail address). Protecting your privacy when processing your personal data is an important matter for us and is part of our business processes, for which we refer to the conditions of UK Data Protection legislation / Swiss Data Protection legislation as our basis. This policy statement explains how we collect and process personal data.
3. Cookies
EAO only collects information about you in the form in which you make it available to us. EAO’s website uses cookies to track visitor preferences and to be able to optimise the website design accordingly. Cookies are small files that are temporarily stored on your hard drive. Most browsers accept cookies automatically. This makes the website more user-friendly and easier to navigate. You may of course view our website without cookies, although not accepting cookies may mean that some of the features of this site will not work properly.
4. Use of your contact details
We use the contact details collected by EAO solely for the purpose of sending you information such as service features, new articles or interesting events that you will find useful when working with EAO products. If you wish to be removed from the mailing list, please send a short notification to this effect to EAO. Your data may be also be forwarded, collected and analysed within the EAO Group insofar as this is necessary to assign you to the correct department of other EAO companies.
5. International data exchange within the EAO Group
EAO is an internationally operational company and as such, your details will be forwarded to the appropriate EAO company, including those outside of the European Economics Association. We will only do this if we are sure that the same regulations for protecting your privacy that we adhere to also apply in that country.
6. Consent to the storage of personal data
By disclosing your personal information to EAO, you are consenting to it being collected, stored and processed in accordance with this policy statement.
7. Personal data
If any of your personal data changes, we would like to know about this and update our database accordingly. You may use the contact form on this website for this purpose, with the comment “Update my information”, or choose any other form of communication. If you have any questions regarding this policy statement or your data as stored by EAO, please contact your EAO representative. Click here to select your sales company.
8. Privacy policy statement regarding the use of Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, text files that are stored on your computer to enable your use of the website to be analysed. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is generally transmitted to and stored on a server at Google in the US. However, should the IP anonymisation function be activated on this website, Google will shorten your IP address before transmission within member states of the European Union or other contracting states to the Treaty on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the US before being shortened. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity and providing the operators of the website with further services relating to website activity and Internet usage. The IP address transmitted from your browser via Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may prevent the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However, please note that in doing so you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You may also prevent the collection and processing of the data generated by the cookie and your website user data (incl. your IP address) by Google by downloading and installing the Browser-Plugin, which is available at the following link http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.Further information regarding this is available at http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en and http://www.google.com/intl/None/policies/privacy/
Please note that on this website Google Analytics has been extended with the code „gat._anonymizeIp();“ , to ensure the anonymised collection of IP addressed (so-called “IP masking”.)
9. Lead Forensiccs
Contained within our website is tracking code from Lead Forensics. Lead Forensics will track activity on the website and provide EAO with information on the IP address of the requesting computer (this data is not anonymised), the date and duration of the user’s visit, and the web pages which the user visits. The Lead Forensics tool complies with the data protection act because it is only providing information that’s readily available in the public domain. The Lead Forensics tool uses IP tracking for identifying visitors and not cookies. It does not, and cannot, provide information WHO has visited the website. It provides information on WHAT company. More information can be found at www.leadforensics.com.
10. Responsible for Privacy Policies - GDPR (EU)
Please contact our responsible by email privacy.policies@eao.com or by mail address with additional information „Responsible Privacy Policies“
This site is operated by EAO Group, Tannwaldstrasse 88, CH-4601 Olten, Switzerland
Responsible for Privacy Policies for EAO Automotive GmbH & Co. KG:
Datenschutz Consulting Dresden GmbH, Andreas Siegemund, Altmarkt 10C,
01067 Dresden. Please read our Privacy Notice carefully.
Privacy Policies3D-LoginSitemapAbout EAOContactLegal NoticeLegal DisclaimerPrivacy Policies
